Thank you for watching!
Oh, there it is, the flowers.
Oh no!
No!
Don't come here!
I'm not going home.
I'm going home, too.
I'm going home too.
I'm sorry, but can I ask you to get in the black car you see there?
I can't... it's the only chance I have.
Please get in.
Nothing. They're accepting it faster.
You two...
What are you scared of? Dash, dash, dash!
I'm hungry.
We haven't had lunch yet.
We were just about to go.
What's this? I'm scared.
I don't like it.
Why?
I'm scared.
There we go. There we go.
What do you mean? There you go.
What's going on?
Pretty for you.
In my life
I wanna be with you
I wanna be mine
Tell me now
If it's a word, I won't let it in
It's up now, it's about
You and me so Buried
I think I have that eye mask.
Can I ask you to put it on?
I can see you.
I know you do.
Oh, I see it!
Here it is!
You're off for a week from today. Get some rest here.
That sucks.
Like you can take the car, or you can take me?
I can take you.
That's great.
Where do you want to go?
Put it on, put it on, put it on, put it on.
Don't take it off until we get there.
I'm afraid, I'm not good with that kind of thing.
Put it on now.
Are you sure?
Put it on.
Are you sure you're going?
We're leaving now, please.
Oh, really?
Really? I'm scared.
I'm really scared. I've never been scared before.
I'm scared. I'm really scared.
Vaah!
Come on, I really don't want to do this. I really don't want to do this. I really don't want to do this.Hey, I really don't want to do that anymore. I really don't want to do that. Seriously, let's not do that.
Wait! What? It's Yuzuan! It's not Yuzuan?
Wait, really? It's not Yuzu-An? It could be!
It's possible! Wait!
You said it's only today. It's the only day we can eat it.
Yuzu-an is too good. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
What? Yuzu-an? Wait, that's possible!
Oh, really, it's possible? Yay!
I'm going to go as Yuzuan.
Oh my God!
I'm going to get pissed.
What? What? Huh?
What? Are we there?
Aah!
You know, you really need to stop now.
I really want you to stop.
I really don't want you to.
You're scaring me.
You said soda.
I'm scared! It's cold!
Reach out with your left hand and it will open.
Keep going.
Wait a minute, I'm scared, machine.
How do they see us?
I'll take it off.
Ready.
Ready, set, go.
Whoa!
What the hell? What is it?
It's a big pile.
Wow!
I'm so happy!
I'm so excited! What's going on?
Oh, my God! I love the colors!
Oh, my God! What's going on?
I see it! There's so many colors!
Oh, my God! I can see the colors!
Yay! I'm so happy!
It was a nice surprise! I'm so happy!
Really? Yes! Really?
So now we want to go make our first mountain! Yay!
This is Mr. Suyama Hochoki, apparently! Yes, have a good day!
Excuse me. Good morning. Good morning.
Oh! How do you do? Yes.
Introductions. Let me introduce you.
This is Mr. Kamioka. I'm Suyama Hochoki Kamioka. Thank you for coming.
We are AmeFlash. Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much for having us.
Now, we will take your ear molds today and prepare the earphones for you.
Clean the line of the ear.
Clean.
It will have the same effect as earplugs.
I will call out to you after I have poured the mold agent into your ears,
First, open and close your mouth two or three times and shift your lower jaw four or five times from side to side.
With the mouth open, I ask them to change the shape of the inside of the ear, but not the same shape as when they are singing,
I would like to have them change the shape and get that mold.
So, after the exercise is over, I will ask them to open their mouths for a minute and wait,
Then I'll ask them to keep their mouth open for a little bit, for five minutes, so it's not too small,
I ask them to open it for five minutes,
Then! It's in!Ta-da! It's in!
It's stuck. My ear.
Do I have to keep my mouth open?
I'm taking the shoulder.
It's shaped like a flower.
They're like earrings.
Oh, I have to open my mouth.
They look like earrings.
They're not cute, so don't use them.
They're cute.
I'm confused.
This one's a melzon. It's cute.
The transparency is cute.
The transparency shows a hint of red or something.
I'm torn.
I'm lost.
They're all the same outside, aren't they?
It's cute, but...
But it's all over my clothes.
Well, you're right, it's kind of flowery.
The great one.
One of the darker ones.
Transparent face
Transparent blue.
Cute.
It's pretty.
You said I should go purple, and then I looked at it.
I thought this clearance was pretty, too.
But I think it's too dark.
If it's even darker...
I think it's better.
I don't know what I'd go with for skin.
This clear yellow or this clear gray.
Transparent gray.
I'm torn.
I can't decide.
I don't know what to do.
It looks good with transparency.
But I wanted to add a hint of sarcasm.
I wanted it to have a touch of sarcasm.
I like it.
There's something I've been wondering about.
This is a candy challenge, right?
So you don't want to do the challenge this time?
No problem.
Why don't you stop digging your own hole?
Let's go karaoke!
I'll be on the radio later.
We were originally going to do karaoke?
We were going to do karaoke in our free time in the fall.
We were going to do karaoke.
You've got karaoke?
Today is the "Ear Beauty Contest"!
What?
It's not so much what's on the inside as what's on the outside.
Like, is it easier to make ear monies?
I guess there's a lot we don't know.
So you're saying that you have a specialist...
You mean you're choosing them for us?
It seems like he's choosing them for us.It seems that the doctor has made his choice.
I'll call him.
Mr. Teacher!
Wow, he's bringing it!
Whose is it?
Huh?
Hana!
Yes!
Hana?
Oh, yeah.
Yes!
Yes, it is.
Yes, the ear canals are straight.
The bend isn't too extreme, so it's pretty straight.
It's not that it's easy to make, but the shape is beautiful.
Yay!
Still looking forward to seeing it finished.
Let's decide on the color and look forward to the next one!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the above!
See you later.
Looking forward to it, everyone.
Looking forward to it.
Oh, no!
Wow!
Ladies and gentlemen, the Japan Games are finally starting!
I knew it, I knew it, genius, lame!
Super bad language!
I knew it!
I knew it, Ichikawa, Ichikawa, I knew it